http://www.producersguild.org/?page=privacy_policy

Search
Search »
Guild
About the PGABecome a Member
Why You Should JoinMembership RequirementsMembership FAQJoin Now
HistoryOfficers, Board & StaffSponsorsPGA NetworkFAQFor Employers
Hire PGA
InternationalFeatured Stories
Members
Member CentralBenefitsActive CommitteesCalendarJobs BoardDues Payment InfoMentoring
Mentoring Shadow ProgramPGA East MentoringPGA West Mentoring
Screener InformationVideo Exclusives
HomeWebinarsConversations WithProduced By Conference
YouTube ChannelMember SearchPGA NewsletterPGA Logo PolicyPGA Policy ManualMember Resource Library
Credits
The Producers MarkProducers Code of CreditsTheatrical
General Credit Guidelines"Produced By" Credit
Short-Form Television
Episodic TelevisionNon-Fiction TelevisionExecutive Producer Credit
Programs
Debra Hill FellowshipAnti-Sexual Harassment GuidelinesMake Your Mark CompetitionPower of Diversity Producing WorkshopPGA Green Production GuideMs. Factor ToolkitContract Services Safety CoursePGA’s COVID Safety ProtocolsPGA Safety InitiativeEmployment Rights of the Producing TeamO-1/O-2 Advisory Opinion Letters
Sponsors
Edit This Favorite
Name:
Category:
Share:
Yes
No, Keep Private
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy tells you how we use and protect your
personal information. It only
covers information that is collected through www.producersguild.org (hereinafter referred to as
the "site”). All users will be
asked to accept this policy and also the site’s Terms and Conditions upon
registration.
This policy does not cover information that may be collected
through sites or software that are linked to the site. If you disclose your information to
others, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information
you disclose to them. We do not
control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the
privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions
before you disclose your personal information to others.
Collection of Data on
the Site
In general, you can browse public areas of www.producersguild.org without
telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about
yourself. Once you give us your
personal information, you are not anonymous to the site.
The site collects and stores information including:
Username;Password;Producers Guild Member ID Number;Email Address;Full Name;Title;Credit and Résumé Information; Phone Numbers;Fax Numbers;Addresses;Payment Information;Photos;Videos;Audio Recordings; andCorrespondence sent through the site.
We also collect and store information from your interactions
with the site; including computer and connection information, statistics on
page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web
log information.
If you choose to provide personal information, you consent
to the transfer and storage of that information on the site’s servers.
Accessing, Reviewing
and Changing Your Personal Information
You can see, review and change most of your personal
information by signing on to www.producersguild.org. Generally, we will not manually modify
your personal information because it is very difficult to verify your identity
remotely.
Once you make a public posting, you may not be able to
change or remove it. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove
your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible.
We retain personal information from closed accounts to
comply with the law, enforce our policies, prevent fraud, assist with any
investigations, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.
Security
We treat data as an asset that must be protected and employ
tools (passwords, user IDs, etc.) to protect your personal information from
unauthorized access and disclosure.
Nevertheless, we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your
personal information or private communications will always remain private. Third parties may unlawfully intercept
or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or
misuse your personal information that they collect from the site.
Please remember that your password is the key to your
account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not
disclose your password to anyone. If you do share your password or your
personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all
actions taken under the name of your account. If your password has been compromised for any reason, you
should immediately notify the site at: info@producersguild.org so that
we can assist you.
Additionally, your User ID is displayed and connected to all
of your activity on the site when you are logged in. If you access the site from a shared computer or unprotected
network (such as a public library or an internet café) certain information
about you, such as your User ID, may also be visible to other individuals who
use the computer after you.
Our Disclosure of
Your Information
We may disclose personal information that you provide to respond
to legal requirements, enforce our policies, or protect anyone's rights,
property, or safety. Such
information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and
regulations.
We may also share your personal information with service
providers, such as website programmers, who help with our business operations.
Without limiting the above, we will not disclose your
personal information to law enforcement, or other third parties without a
subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, unless we
believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to
prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal
activity.
Cookies
We use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard
drive) on some of our pages to do the following:
Collect statistics on our web page flow; Customize our services, content and advertising;
and To help identify you and maintain your signed-in
status.
Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that
they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session.
You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits.
You may encounter cookies from third parties that the
Producers Guild does not control.
For example, if you view a web page created by one of the Guild’s
advertisers, there may be a cookie placed by that web page. The Producers Guild and its site cannot
be responsible for these cookies.
Marketing
We will not sell or rent personal information that you
provide to the site to third parties without your explicit consent. We may use your information along with
information we collect from other users to improve and personalize our
services, content and advertising.
No Spam, Spyware or
Spoofing
This site does not tolerate spam. You may not add any user to your mailing list (email or
physical mail) without that user’s express consent. Additionally, you may not use the site’s communication
tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate this policy or
the site’s Terms and Conditions.
Please report site-related spam or spoof emails to: info@producersguild.org.
Children Under Age 13
We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information
from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to
register. If you are under 13,
please do not attempt to register for this site or send any information about
yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email
address. No one under age 13
may provide any personal information to the site.
In the event that we learn that we have collected personal
information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent,
we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we
might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at info@producersguild.org.
Children Between the
Ages of 13 and 18
We recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their
parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to
anyone over the Internet.
General
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the
amended terms on this site. If we
make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, via email, or
through notice on the site’s home page.
All amended terms automatically take effect 30 days after
they are initially posted on the site.
If you have questions or concerns about any changes, please contact us at: info@producersguild.org.
You may also contact us by mail at:
Producers
Guild of America Website8530
Wilshire Blvd., Suite 450Beverly
Hills, CA 90211Information on YourMembership.com and their privacy policy.
SEE THE DIGITAL EDITION
Sign In
Remember Me
Forgot your password?Haven't registered yet?
moreCalendar
10/14/2020Tips from the Field: Producers Making their Way Back into Production - 10/1410/21/2020Tips from the Field: Producers Making their Way Back into Production - 10/21
Online Surveys
Odd Numbers
Latest News
more
View RSS feed
HomeMember Central
Sign In/Sign Out SearchNewsVideosContact Us Privacy PolicyTerms of Use
About the PGABecome a MemberProducers Code of CreditsPGA AwardsProduced By ConferenceProduced By Magazine
Association Management Software Powered by YourMembership  ::  Legal
